weedtracker.com 2013-10-15

# Privacy Policy | Dispensary Weed

This document outlines how Dogpatch Media, LLC dba Weedtracker (“Weedtracker”Â) has established this privacy policy to explain to you how your information is protected, collected and used, which may be updated by Weedtracker from time to time. Weedtracker will provide notice of materially significant changes to this privacy policy by posting notice on the Weedtracker website (the “Website”). The latest version of the Privacy Policy posted in the “Policy” category of the “Pages” section of the site.

**1\. Privacy disclosures:**

Account information is password-protected. Passwords are encrypted and Weedtracker employees will never ask for your password. Keep your password safe. 

Weedtracker runs banner ads, pop ups, pop unders, and other types of commercial ads. We engage in cross-marketing or link-referral programs with other sites. We employ tracking devices for marketing purposes (“cookies”, “web beacons,” single-pixel gifs). You should be aware that information and data may be automatically collected through the use of “cookies”. “Cookies” are small text files a web site can use to recognize repeat users and allows Weedtracker to compile non-personally identifiable, aggregate data in order to improve the Website and to target its advertising. However, Weedtracker will not send you unsolicited communications for marketing purposes. 

Weedtracker, or people who post on Weedtracker, may provide links to third party websites, which may have different privacy practices. We are not responsible for, nor have any control over, the privacy policies of those third party websites, and encourage all users to read the privacy policies of each and every website visited. 

Search engines and other sites not affiliated with Weedtracker – including archive.org, google.com, and groups.yahoo.com – archive or otherwise make available Weedtracker postings. Please note that if you give out personal information online – for example, on the public forums, in the chat rooms, or in the chat IM feature – that information can be collected and used by third parties. Although we strive to protect our users’ privacy, we cannot guarantee the security of information you post in these forums and have no control over how such third parties may use your information. Bulletin board postings should be considered non-confidential. You disclose such information at your own risk. 

Weedtracker does not knowingly collect any information from persons under the age of 18. If Weedtracker learns that a posting is by a person under the age of 18, Weedtracker will remove that post.

**2\. Data we collect:**

We only collect your email address, for purposes such as sending self-publishing and confirmation emails, authenticating user accounts, providing subscription email services, registering for forums, etc. Weedtracker does not store credit card information. Credit card transactions are transmitted to a financial gateway, and we endeavor to protect the security of your payment information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology. We may collect personal information if you provide it in feedback or comments, post it on our classifieds or interactive forums, or if you contact us directly. Please do not post any personal information on the Website that you expect to keep private. Our web logs collect standard web log entries for each page served, including your IP address, page URL, and timestamp. Web logs help us to diagnose problems with our server, to administer the Website, and to otherwise provide our service to you.

**3\. Data we store:**

All bulletin board postings are stored in our database, even after Ã¢â‚¬Å“deletion,Ã¢â‚¬Â and may be archived elsewhere. Our web logs and other records are stored indefinitely. Although we make good faith efforts to store the information in a secure operating environment that is not available to the public, we cannot guarantee complete security.

**4\. Archiving and display of Weedtracker postings by search engines and other sites:**

Search engines and other sites not affiliated with Weedtracker – including archive.org, google.com, and groups.yahoo.com – archive or otherwise make available Weedtracker postings.

**5\. Circumstances in which Weedtracker may release information:**

Weedtracker may disclose information about its users if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to respond to subpoenas, court orders, or other legal process. Weedtracker may also disclose information about its users to law enforcement officers or others, in the good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to: enforce our Terms of Use; respond to claims that any posting or other content violates the rights of third-parties; or protect the rights, property, or personal safety of Weedtracker, its employees, owners, users or the general public.

**6\. International Users:**

By visiting our Website and providing us with data, you acknowledge and agree that due to the international dimension of Weedtracker we may use the data collected in the course of our relationship for the purposes identified in this policy or in our other communications with you, including the transmission of information outside your resident jurisdiction. In addition, please understand that such data may be stored on servers located in the United States. By providing us with your data, you consent to the transfer of such data.

**7\. Notification of Changes to Privacy Policy:**

Any and all changes to the Privacy Policy shall be posted to the Website upon implementation. Users are encouraged to check the Website for updates and changes to the Privacy Policy.

**8\. Google Analytics Informations**

This website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. (“Google”). Google Analytics uses “cookies”, which are text files placed on your computer, to help the website analyze how users use the site. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website (including your IP address) will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States. Google will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of the website, compiling reports on website activity for website operators and providing other services relating to website activity and internet usage. Google may also transfer this information to third parties where required to do so by law, or where such third parties process the information on Google’s behalf. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser, however please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of this website. By using this website, you consent to the processing of data about you by Google in the manner and for the purposes set out above. 

_**Last Updated: January, 28, 2011  
Effective Date: July 29, 2008 **_
